<idea-plugin version="1">
  <id>netsuite.tools.plugin</id>
  <name>NetSuite Tools For WebStorm</name>
  <version>1.1.6</version>

  <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>

  <description><![CDATA[
      <div>
        <div>
          <a href="https://github.com/Topher84/NetSuite-Tools-For-WebStorm">[GitHub] NetSuite Tools For WebStorm</a> <br />
          <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/creece84">[LinkedIn] Plugin Author</a>
        </div>
        <div>
        </div>
        <div>
          <br /><br />
          Open source WebStorm IDE plugin that uses NetSuite SuiteTalk 2017.1 WSDL to provide the ability to:
          <ol>
            <li>Specify <b><i>any</i></b> NetSuite File Cabinet Folder as the project root directory or select from SuiteScripts or SuiteBundles listing</li>
            <li>Upload Folder(s) and File(s) to NetSuite File Cabinet</li>
            <li>Compare local File(s) against NetSuite File Cabinet</li>
          </ol>
        </div>
      </div>
    ]]></description>
  <change-notes><![CDATA[
  <ul>
      <li>1.0.1 Added fix to correctly pull back Administrator and Full Access accounts</li>
      <li>1.0.2 Added fix to correctly search for files that share the same name as the root at the beginning</li>
      <li>1.0.3 Added fix to correctly search for files with the same name in the root and multiple sub-folders</li>
      <li>1.0.4 Added fix to potentially correct a "context passing" exception that randomly occurs when uploading files</li>
      <li>1.0.5 Added fixes for several reported null pointer exceptions and some very minor code cleanup</li>
      <li>1.0.6 Added fix to UTF-8 encode e-mail and password to account for special characters</li>
      <li>1.0.7 Added fix to not overwrite file properties when uploading files</li>
      <li>1.0.8 Added fix to not show success when files fail to upload and also now display upload failure detail</li>
      <li>1.0.9 Added enhancement to save files before uploading and some code cleanup</li>
      <li>1.0.10 [v2016.3+] Added new password storage method(s) introduced for 2016.3 releases to replace the deprecated implementation</li>
      <li>1.0.11 Added enhancement to use new 2016.2 WSDL</li>
      <li>1.0.12 Added enhancement to use Background Tasks (asynchronous processing) for file uploading and comparisons so the IDE does not appear to "freeze" due to original Actions synchronously processing by default</li>
      <li>1.0.13 Added fix to get correct release preview account URLs</li>
      <li>1.1.0 Added 2017.1 WSDL support</li>
      <li>1.1.1 Updated environments to only contain sandbox and production. Domains are changing to a single domain system so the only two (2) domains that should exist now are sandbox and production. Sandbox will eventually be removed since all domains will point to production.</li>
      <li>1.1.2 Added 2018.2 upload issue from GitHub issue #38 which includes the authentication header with each request. Note that this does not fix upcoming 2FA issue(s). Also added 2018.1 Records Browser link.</li>
      <li>1.1.3 Removed the only ADMIN/FULL role account selection to allow for selection of custom roles for 2FA that are not admin/full access.</li>
      <li>1.1.4 Fixed uploading files with captions containing a length of > 40. Updated error messaging on upload tasks to contain the error message. Added a 2FA note when choosing an account.</li>
      <li>1.1.5 Added error message when attempting to upload a file and the configured NetSuite account is no longer valid.</li>
      <li>1.1.6 Added error message when attempting to compare file(s) and the configured NetSuite account is no longer valid.</li>
  </ul>
    ]]>
  </change-notes>

  <idea-version since-build="163.0"/>

  <actions>
    <group id="com.action.netsuitetools" text="NetSuite Tools" description="NetSuite Tools" popup="true">
      <add-to-group group-id="ProjectViewPopupMenu" anchor="last"  />
      <action id="com.action.netsuitetools.setupproject" class="actions.SetupProjectAction" text="Set Up Project"
              description="Set Up Project"/>
      <action id="com.action.netsuitetools.showprojectsettings" class="actions.ShowProjectSettingsAction"
              text="Show Project Settings" description="Show Project Settings"/>
      <action id="com.action.netsuitetools.changeprojectsettings" class="actions.ChangeProjectSettingsAction"
              text="Change Project Settings" description="Change Project Settings"/>
      <action id="com.action.netsuitetools.upload" class="actions.UploadAction"
              text="Upload Selected File(s)" description="Upload Selected File(s) to NetSuite File Cabinet"/>
      <action id="com.action.netsuitetools.comparewithfilecabinet" class="actions.CompareWithFileCabinetAction"
              text="Compare With File Cabinet" description="Compare Selected File(s) with File Cabinet"/>
      <action id="com.netsuitetools.recordsbrowser" class="actions.RecordsBrowserAction"
              text="2018.1 Records Browser" description="2018.1 Records Browser"/>
    </group>
  </actions>
</idea-plugin>